Guide to the Sid Ramin Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Sid Ramin Papers,
[ca. 1957]-1962
Ramin, Sid.
172 items (8 oversize boxes)
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New York, NY.
4079249
Biographical Note
Composer, conductor, arranger for Broadway and Hollywood musicals and for television shows.
Scope and Content
Song copies and the scores of the original orchestrations for the Broadway musicals Gypsy, A Funny Thing Happened On The Way To The Forum, and I Can Get It For You Wholesale. Also, scores for the movie and stage orchestration and symphonic suite for West Side Story; and the original orchestral scores for the motion picture, Around The World In Eighty Days. The orchestration for this film was the work of Leo Shuken and Sid Cutner.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into 14 series:
Series I: Gypsy
Series II: A Funny Thing Happened of the Way to the Forum
Series III: I Can Get It For You Wholesale
Series IV: Around the World in 80 Days
Series V: Stiletto
Series VI: West Side Story
Series VII: President Kennedy Anniversary
Series VIII: New Thresholds in Sound by Sid Ramin and Orchestra
Series IX: The Big Band Sound of Sid Ramin
Series X: President Johnson Overtures
Series XI: Mass
Series XII: 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue
Series XIII: Jerome Robbins' Broadway
Series XIV: The Red Shoes
Subjects
Musicals.; Motion picture music--Scores.; Motion picture music, Arranged.; Arrangement (Music); Instrumentation and orchestration.; Musical scores.; Composers.; Conductors (Music).
Access Restrictions
This collection has no restrictions.
This collection is located on-site.
Acquisition
1968 M-68 Ramin, Sid Gift
- Series I: Gypsy
  "Gypsy." A Musical Fable. Book by Arthur Laurents, Music by Jule Styne, Lyrics by Stephen Sondheim. Produced, directed and choreographed by Jerome Robbins. Starring Ethel Merman. Orchestration by Sid Ramin and Robert Ginzler. Produced in Spring 1959.
  - Subseries I.1: Songs Used for Orchestration
    The original song copies used for the orchestration of the show by Sld Ramin with Robert Ginzler. The song copies have the original marking by Sid Ramin. Quarto, (9 3/4" x 12 1/2").
    - You'll Never Get Away From Me., (11 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 1)
    - Together Wherever We Go., (9 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 2)
    - Small World., (7 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 3)
    - Mama's Talkin' Soft., (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 4)
    - All I Need Is The Girl., (10 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 5)
    - Some People., (11 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 6)
    - If Mamma Was Married., (13 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 7)
    - The Cow Song., (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 8)
    - Let Me Entertain You., (4 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 9)
    - Mr. Goldstone., (22 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 10)
    - You Gotta Get A Gimmick., (16 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 11)
    - Broadway., (11 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 12)
    - Mother's Day., (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 13)
    - Little Lamb, Little Lamb., (4 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 14)
    - Ev'rything's Coming Up Roses., (10 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 15)
    - Smile Girls., (11 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 16)
  - Subseries I.2: Songs Not Used for Orchestration
    The song copies were written for the show but were never orchestrated or used.
    - Nice She Ain't., (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 1)
    - Surprise., (Original 3 page manuscript in the hand of Jule Styne. ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 1.3 Scores for Pre-recording
    The scores of the original orchestrations for pre-recording used a "source" music in the show.
    - June is a Jew, So Change It to Clare., (6 Pages 44, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 1)
    - Zip My Stripper., (9 Pages 45, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 2)
    - The Bloozy Cool., (8 Pages 47, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 3)
    - Presto Bing Flip., (12 Pages 92, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 4)
    - Figure 8 Waltz., (13 Pages 96, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 5)
    - The Exotic., (6 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 257, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 1.4 Scores of Original Orchestrations
    Original orchestrations by Sid Ramin with Robert Ginzler. With original corrections, markings and notes in the hand of Sid Ramin. Folio, (11" x 17").
    - The Gypsy Overture., (40 Pages 286, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 1)
    - Ethel's Entrance., (23 Pages 180, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 2)
    - Some People., (32 Pages 244, Bars Supplement: 3, Pages 20, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 3)
    - Seattle To Los Angeles., (16 Pages 94, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 4)
    - Small World, (31 Pages 64, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 5)
    - Baby June and Newsboys (Part One and Two), (16 Pages 123, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 6)
    - Recitation and Military:, (11 Pages 81, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 7)
    - Children's Military Routine., (6 Pages 42, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 8)
    - Mr. Goldstone. Part One., (19 Pages 151, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 9a.)
    - Mr. Goldstone. Part Two, (7 Pages 39, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 9b.)
    - Mr. Goldstone. Part Three, (9 Pages 71, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 9c.)
    - Goldstone To Lamb., (2 Pages 12, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 10)
    - Little Lamb., (19 Pages 124, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 11)
    - Little Lamb To Restaurant., (3 Pages 16, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 12)
    - You'll Never ,Get Away From Me., (15 Pages 99, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 13)
    - Broadway., (31 Pages 211, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 14)
    - If Mama Was Married, (28 Pages 218, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 15)
    - Montage I., (7 Pages 37, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 16)
    - All I Need Is The Girl., (10 Pages 68, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 258, Folder 17)
    - Ev'rything's Coming Up Roses., (28 Pages 220, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 18)
    - Entr'Acte New., (13 Pages 77, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 19)
    - Entr'Acte Old., (20 Pages 132, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 20)
    - Toreadorables., (17 Pages 101, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 21)
    - Together., (23 Pages 168, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 22a.)
    - Additional Material, (9 Pages 81, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 22b.)
    - Together Tag, (7 Pages 52, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 23)
    - Montage II., (5 Pages 38, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 24)
    - Rose Underscore, Act II.Scene IV, (10 Pages 73, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 25)
    - You Gotta Get A Gimmick., (26 Pages 167, Bars Additional Material 7, Pages ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 26)
    - Small World Reprise., (5 Pages 28, Bars Additional Material 5, Pages 27, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 27)
    - Gypsy Strip., (15 Pages 108, Bars Additional Material 20, Pages 150, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 28)
    - After Bathroom., (3 Pages 19, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 29)
    - Curtain - Act II., (2 Pages 14, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 30)
    - Bows., (2 Pages 16, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 31)
    - Mama' s Turn., (22 Pages 144, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 32)
    - Exit March., (21 Pages 125, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 33)
    - If Mama Was Married. Utility, (11 Pages 86, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 34)
    - All I Need. Utility., (10 Pages 38, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 35)
    - You'll Never Get Away, (10 Pages 32, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 36)
    - Small World., (10 Pages 38, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 37)
    - Some People., (18 Pages 72, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 38)
    - Extra. Utility., (10 Pages 40, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 39)
    - Cow Recitation, (13 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 259, Folder 40)
- Series II: A Funny Thing Happened of the Way to the Forum
  "A Funny Thing Happened On The Way To The Forum.-" Book by Burt Schevelove and Larry Gelbart, Music and Lyrics by Stephen Sondheim. Directed by George Abbott. Choreography by Jack Cole. Starring Zero Mostel. Orchestration by Sid Ramin and Irwin Kostal. Produced in Spring 1962.
  - Subseries II.1 Songs Used for Orchestration
    The original song copies used for the orchestration of the show by Sid Ramin and Irwin Kostal. The following song copies have the original marking by the orchestrators Sid Ramin and Irwin Kostal. Quarto, (9 3/4" x 12 1/2").
    - Once Upon a Time., (8 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 1)
    - Free., ( 15Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 2)
    - Free., (16 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 701)
    - Love I Hear., ( 6Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 3)
    - Love I Hear, (7 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 701)
    - Pretty Little Picture, ( 12Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 4)
    - Love Is Going Around., ( 3Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 5)
    - Love Is Going Around, (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 701)
    - That Dirty Old Man., ( 5 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 6)
    - That Dirty Old Man, (5 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 701)
    - Lovely., ( 4Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 6a.)
    - Bring Me My Bride, ( 11Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 7)
    - Bring Me My Bride, (11 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 701)
    - The House Of Marcus Lycus., ( 9Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 8)
    - The House of Marcus Lycus, (9 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 701)
    - The House Of Marcus Lycus. (Revised Copy), ( 9Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 9)
    - Bring Me My Bride Reprise., ( 2Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 10)
    - Bring Me My Bride Reprise, (2 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 701)
    - Funeral Sequence., ( 11Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 11)
    - Funeral Sequence, (11 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 701)
    - That'll Show Him, (6 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 701)
  - Subseries II.2 Songs with notes by Sondheim
    Song copies have notes and original music in the hand of the composer Stephen Sondhelm. (Quarto, 9 3/4" x 12 1/2").
    - Lovely., ( 3Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 1)
    - I Do Like You., ( 12Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 2)
    - That'll Show Him., ( 3Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 3)
    - Everybody Ought To Have A Maid., ( 20Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 4)
    - Chase., ( 3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 5)
  - Subseries II.3 Scores of Original Orchestrations
    The scores with the original corrections, markings and notes by the orchestrators Sid Ramin and Irwin Kostal. Folio, (11" x 17").
    - Overture. Used only in New Haven opening., (10 Pages 39, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 1a.)
    - Overture. New, (22 Pages 169, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 1b.)
    - Love Is Golng Around., ( 14 Pages 78, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 2)
    - Comedy Tonight., (74 Pages 422, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 3)
    - Set The Scene., (1 Pages 4, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 4)
    - Love I Hear (Used Prior to New York opening), ( 21Pages 82, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 5a.)
    - Love I Hear, ( 16Pages 94, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 5b.)
    - Free., ( 26Pages 182, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 6)
    - The House Of Marcus Lycus., ( 28Pages 154, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 7)
    - Courtesans Exit., (2 Pages 10, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 8)
    - Lovely., (17 Pages 92, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 9)
    - Pretty Little Picture., ( 24Pages 130, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 260, Folder 10)
    - Everybody Ought To Have A Maid., ( 21Pages 119, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 11)
    - Everybody Ought To Have A Maid. Encore., ( 9Pages 50, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 12)
    - Mornpipe, ( 3Pages 14, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 13)
    - Courtesans Entrance., ( 2Pages 10, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 14)
    - I'm Calm., ( 15Pages 88, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 15)
    - Impossible., ( 19Pages 99, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 16)
    - Fanfare I, ( 2Pages 4, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 17)
    - Bring Me My Bride., (16 Pages 92, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 18)
    - Fanfare.II., (1 Page 1, Bar ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 19)
    - End Act I, (2 Pages 9, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 20)
    - Entr'acte., ( 19Pages 134, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 21)
    - Opening. Act II., ( 1Page 5, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 22)
    - Love Is Going Around. Underscore, ( 3Pages 28, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 23)
    - Back to the Plot, (1 Page 2, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 24)
    - Soldiers' Free., ( 9Pages 52, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 25)
    - That Dirty Old Man., (15 Pages 58, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 26)
    - That'll Show Him., ( 13Pages 73, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 27a.)
    - That'll Show Him. New (replaced a), ( 16Pages 89, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 27b.)
    - Lovely. Reprise., ( 13Pages 75, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 28)
    - Funeral Sequence., ( 23Pages 98, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 29)
    - Zero., ( 1Page 4, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 30)
    - Pre-Echo Song. Chase, ( 7Pages 29, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 31)
    - Echo Song., ( 9Pages 36, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 32a.)
    - Echo Song. New (replaced a)., ( 13Pages 49, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 32b.)
    - Chase., (32 Pages 151, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 33)
    - Chase. Part Two., (11 Pages 50, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 34)
    - Finale Act II., (13 Pages 73, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 35)
    - Bows., (6 Pages 36, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 261, Folder 36)
- Series III: I Can Get It For You Wholesale
  "I Can Got It For You Wholesale." Book by Jerome Weidman. Music and Lyrics by Harold Rome, directed by Arthur Laurents, musical directions by Lehman Engel, choreography by Herbert Ross, Orchestration by Sid Ramin and Arthur Beck. Starring Barbra Streisand. Produced in Spring 1962.
  - Subseries III.1 Scores of Original Orchestrations
    The complete scores of the original orchestrations with notes by Sid Ramin and Arthur Beck. Folio, (11" x 17")
    - The Way Things Are., ( 11Pages 31, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 1)
    - Train Music., ( 1 Page 4, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 2)
    - Who Knows. Utility., ( 6Pages 36, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 3)
    - When Gemini Meets Capricorn., (17 Pages 119, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 4)
    - I'm Not A Well Man., ( 13Pages 98, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 5)
    - Into Money Scene., (2 Pages 17, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 6)
    - Lead into Money Scene., ( 1 Page 5, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 7)
    - The Sound Of Money., ( 15Pages 118, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 8)
    - The Sound Of Money. Dance., ( 19Pages 115, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 9)
    - The Family Way., ( 24Pages 186, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 10)
    - Too Soon., ( 17Pages 132, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 11)
    - When Gemini Meets Capricorn. Utility., ( 7Pages 52, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 12)
    - Who Knows., ( 18Pages 142, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 13)
    - Into Scene X., ( 9Pages 65, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 14)
    - Have I Told You lately., ( 18Pages 136, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 15)
    - Ballad Of The Garment Trade, ( 35Pages 271, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 16)
    - Fashion Show., ( 15Pages 130, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 17)
    - Ballad Of The Garment Trade. Utility, (5 Pages 36, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 18)
    - Entr'acte., (18 Pages 100, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 19)
    - Into Scene I Act II., (1 Page 8, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 20)
    - A Gift Today., (24 Pages 174, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 21)
    - Bar Mitzbah To Marmelstein., (8 Pages 60, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 22)
    - Miss Marmelstein., (11 Pages 85, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 23)
    - Sound Of Money. Underscore., (3 Pages 19, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 24)
    - Lead Into Money Scene., ( 1 Page 5, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 25)
    - What's In It For Me, (24 Pages 158, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 26)
    - Into Scene II.IV., (3 Pages 22, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 27)
    - A Funny Thing Happened., (18 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 28)
    - A Funny Thing Happened. Utility., (8 Pages 68, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 29)
    - After A Funny Thing Happened., (3 Pages 24, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 30)
    - What Are They Doing To Us Now., (18 Pages 136, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 31)
    - What Are They Doing. Dance, (24 Pages 142, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 32)
    - After Doing To Us Now., (1 Page 8, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 33)
    - Eat A Little Something., (16 Pages 125, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 34)
    - After Eat., (1 Page 9, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 35)
    - End Of Show Sequence., (4 Pages 30, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 36)
    - The Sound Of Money. Utility., (5 Pages 38, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 262, Folder 37)
- Series IV: Around the World in 80 Days
  "Around The World In Eighty Days." Screenplay by S. J. Perelman based on the Jules Verne novel. Music by. Victor Young. Choreography by Paul Godkln. Directed by Michael Andersen, produced by Michael Todd, 1957.
  - Subseries IV.1 Scores of Original Orchestrations
    The original orchestral scores used in the scoring of the motion picture. The orchestration was done by Leo Shuken and Sid Cutner. Manuscript music of the scores in hands of the orchestrators Leo Shuken and Sid Cutner, (with corrections and notes by the orchestrators).
    - Introduction To Sky Symphony., (2 Pages 7, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 1)
    - A New Introduction To Sky Symphony., (16 Pages 62, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Sky Symphony. II, ( 27Pages 108, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Sky Symphony. III, (8 Pages 31, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 4)
    - Prairie Sail Car., (41 Pages 161, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 5)
    - Interlude., ( 23Pages 89, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 6)
    - Chinese Misterioso., ( 8Pages 30, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 7)
    - Fujiyama Liquid Music., ( 1Page 4, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 8)
    - Yokohama Children., ( 3 Pages 12, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 9)
    - Hong Kong Chinese Dive., (15 Pages 58, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 10)
    - Passepartout Bicycle., ( 33Pages 131, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 11)
    - Epilogue., ( 31Pages 124, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 12)
    - Epilogue. Part I New., ( 25Pages 98, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 13)
    - Epilogue. Part II., ( 25Pages 99, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 14)
    - Epilogue. Part II. Supplement., ( 40Pages 160, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 15)
    - Epilogue. Part III., ( 28Pages 110, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 16)
    - Epilogue. Part IV., ( 35Pages 138, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 263, Folder 17)
- Series V: Stiletto
  By Harold Bobbins, Music by Sid Ramin, Produced in 1969.
  - Subseries V.1 Sketches
    Original manuscript sketches by Sid Ramin in preparation for the score.
    - Sketches, (68 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Subseries V.2 Scores of Original Orchestrations
    The complete original orchestral score in manuscript. Folio, 393 sheets. Composed and arranged by Sid Ramin.
    - Reel 1 Part A: "Rape in the Barn", (6 Pages 21, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Reel 1 Part 1, (21 Pages 82, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Reel 1 Part 2: "Main Title", (27 Pages 204, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Reel 1 Parts 3-4, (10 Pages 37, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Reel 2 Part 2, (16 Pages 62, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Reel 2 Part 3, (7 Pages 27, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 6)
    - Reel 3 Part 1, (9 Pages 35, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 7)
    - Reel 4 Part 3A: "Flashback.", (15 Pages 58, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 8)
    - Reel 4 Part 4, (3 Pages 9, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 9)
    - Reel 4 Part 5, (5 Pages 17, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 10)
    - Reel 4 Part 6, (13 Pages 49, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 11)
    - Reel 5 Part 1, (7 Pages 51, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 12)
    - Reel 5 Part 3, (11 Pages 41, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 13)
    - Reel 5 Part 3, (5 Pages 53, Bars Revised for album "Goat Island.") (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 14)
    - Reel 5 Part 4, (6 Pages 21, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 264, Folder 15)
    - Reel 6 Part 1, (9 Pages 35, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 16)
    - Reel 6 Part 2, (9 Pages 33, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 17)
    - Reel 6 Part 3: Overlap., (4 Pages 16, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 18)
    - Reel 6 Part 4, (2 Pages 5, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 19)
    - Reel 7 Part 1, (7 Pages 26, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 20a)
    - Reel 7 Part 2, (3 Pages 10, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 20b)
    - Reel 7 Part 4, (18 Pages 140, Bars "Source": 12 pages, 101 bars. "Vocal Insert": 6 pages, 39 bars) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 21)
    - Reel 8 Part 2 - part I: "Northwest Corner Facing East." Overlap., (17 Pages 66, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 22)
    - Reel 8 Part 2 - parts II - III. Overlap., (7 Pages 25, Bars "Skylight": 2 pages, 6 bars. "Tension, Anyone?": 5 pages, 19 bars) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 23)
    - Reel 8 Part 2 - part IV: "Underwater Fight." Overlap., (32 Pages 127, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 24)
    - Reel 8 Part 3: "Motorcycle Waiting.", (16 Pages 61, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 25)
    - Reel 9 Part A: "You're Lying.", (7 Pages 25, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 26)
    - Reel 9 Part 1, (16 Pages 63, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 27)
    - Reel 10 Part 2: "Illeanna's Dilemma.", (2 Pages 8, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 28)
    - Reel 10 Part 3: "The Tram.", (14 Pages 54, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 29)
    - Reel 11 Part 1: "Confrontation.", (36 Pages 102, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 30)
    - Reel 11 Part 2: "In the Tunnel.", (10 Pages 38, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 31)
    - Reel 11 Part 3: "End Titles.", (3 Pages 12, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 32)
    - Sugar In the Rain (Vocal), (19 Pages 72, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 33)
    - Illeanna's Theme, (20 Pages 76, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 265, Folder 34)
- Series VI: West Side Story
  Book by Arthur Laurents, Music by Leonard Bernstein, Lyrics by Stephen Sondheim
  - Subseries VI.1 Scores for Broadway Production
    Produced on Broadway in the fall of 1957. The complete original orchestral score arranged by Leonard Bernstein, Sid Ramin and Irwin Kostal for the Broadway production is contained in five volumes. There are also original orchestral scores for individual songs. The scores have manuscript notes, revisions, additions, and corrections by Bernstein, Ramin, and Kostal. Folio.
    - Volume 1: "The Prologue", "Cool" and "The Rumble"., (123 Pages. Blue print scratch copy. Leonard Bernstein - 12 pages of manuscript notes, revisions and additions. Sid Ramin and Irwin Kostal - 73 pages of manuscript notes, revisions and additions.) (Box Flat Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Volume 2: "Jet Song" - 40 pages; "The Ballet Sequence" -55 pages; "A Boy Like That" - 31 pages; "Taunting Scene" - 11 pages; "Finale" - 9 pages., (146 Pages Leonard Bernstein - 55 pages of manuscript notes, revisions and additions. Sid Ramin and Irwin Kostal - 66 page of manuscript notes, revisions and additions.) (Box Flat Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Volume 3: "The Temporary Overture" - 53 pages; "Something's Coming Utility" - 4 pages; "Death Hall Sequence" - 46 pages; "Maria Cha Cha" - 6 pages; "Meeting Scene" - 9 pages; "Meeting Scene A" - 9 pages, (127Pages Leonard Bernstein - 10 pages of manuscript notes, revisions and additions. Sid Ramin and Irwin Kostal - 64 pages of manuscript notes, revisions and additions.) (Box Flat Box 266, Folder 3)